Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Roy Glah papers, 1947-2003 and undated RL.00704
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials, 1991-2001 and undated; 6
  - Videocassettes, 1991-2001 and undated; 9
    - North America Managers Meeting, 1999 (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-046)
    - North America Managers Meeting--Best work for the last 90 days, 1999 (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-047)
    - Roy Glah food video, undated (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-048)
    - Oprah new edit 2:02, undated (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-049)
    - Prepared Foods Interview #4, 1994 (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-050)
    - Prepared Foods Interview #7, 1994 (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-051)
    - Presentation reel--Latin America Abruption, 1994 (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-052)
      22 spots: California Lottery; 7-Eleven; French's; Bell Atlantic; Kit Kat; Schick; ESSO; Timotei; Haagen Dazs; Ford; Lubriderm; Chiclets; Lever 2000; De Beers; Ken'L Ration; Pow Wow; Kodak
    - Quality and Cost in Advertising--Board of Directors Meeting, 1993 (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-053)
      19 spots: Little Caesar; Pepsi; Timex; Continental Tires; Chanel; Nike 180; British Knights; Sinutab; Magnavox; Merrill Lynch; EPT; Lever 2000; Chicken Tonight; Coke Classic; Honda Prelude; Volkswagen; De Beers
    - Quality and Cost in Advertising--Board of Directors Meeting, 1993 (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-054)
    - Quality and Cost in Advertising--Bangkok, 1993 (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-055)
      19 spots: Little Caesar; Pepsi; Timex; Continental Tires; Chanel; Nike 180; British Knights; Magnavox; Merrill Lynch; California Lottery; Lever 2000; Chicken Tonight; Coke Classic; Honda Prelude; Volkswagen; De Beers
    - Quality and Cost in Advertising--Bangkok PAL, 1993 (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-056)
    - Quality and Cost in Advertising "Abruption"--Kraft Asia Pacific Advertising Conference, Philippines, 1995 (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-057)
      19 spots: Oscar Mayer; French's; Bell Atlantic; Kit Kat; Schick; ESSO; Clairol; Haagen Dazs; Ford; Lubriderm; Nova Language School; De Beers; Ken'L Ration; Lever Drive; Kodak
    - Quality and Cost in Advertising--Burt Manning presentation reel, 1994 (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-058)
      20 spots: 7-eleven; French's; Bell Atlantic; Kit Kat; Schick; ESSO; Oscar Mayer; Timotei; Haagen Dazs; Ford; Lubriderm; Lever 2000; De Beers; Ken'L Ration; Greek Police; Kodak; Karwei; Rolex`
    - Retail Realities: Our Thoughts on Acquiring and Retaining Retail Clients--"You Don't Have to Yell to Sell", circa 2000 (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-059)
    - SCPF (Spain) showreel, 2000 (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-060)
      19 spots: BMW; Evax; Panama Jack; RBA; INDQ; Mujer 21; KAS; ALCER; IKEA
    - Snack and Fast Food Reference Reel, undated (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-061)
    - State of the Agency Speech, 1997 (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-062)
    - Thompson Total Manning (Burt Manning tribute), undated (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-063)
    - Town Hall Meeting--Bill Hamilton reel, undated (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-064)
    - TVC reel for North America Managers Meeting, 1999 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-065)
      107 spots: Ford; Kohl's; White Castle; Qwest; Thermasilk; Project Return; Hall's; CBS Medscape; Schick; Alloy.com; De Beers; Lever 2000; Scott Towels; Children Now; Merrill Lynch; Bailey's; J&B; Nabisco; Kraft; Nestle; Coco's; Shark Wire; Tim Horton; Star TV; KD Easy Mac; Kleenex; Group Action
    - Working Mom Age 25, San Francisco (Burt Manning project), undated (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-066)
    - Working Mom Age 39, San Francisco (Burt Manning project), undated (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL00704-UMATIC-067)
    - Ad Age/Ad Club Luncheon reel, 1991 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL00704-VHS-001)
    - Brand. New. Ideas., undated (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL00704-VHS-002)
    - Chris Jones Chicago remarks, undated (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL00704-VHS-003)
    - Chris Jones Nestle meeting, 2000 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL00704-VHS-004)
    - Creating Impact in Advertising--Conference Board speech version 2, 1999 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL00704-VHS-005)
    - Food long final, undated (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL00704-VHS-006)
    - Food rough cut #1 A-E, undated (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL00704-VHS-007)
    - Ford Motor Company "Ticket Caper", undated (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL00704-VHS-008)
    - Groupaction (Montreal) agency demo, undated (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL00704-VHS-009)
    - Rolex 1995-1996 Co-Op Advertising Television Commercial Sampler (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL00704-VHS-010)
    - Sam Meek Seminar Madrid "Abruption" PAL, 1994 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL00704-VHS-011)
    - Spring Showreel, JWT London, 2001 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL00704-VHS-012)
    - Summary interviews (some, not all), undated (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL00704-VHS-013)
    - TTB Awards, undated (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL00704-VHS-014)
      12 spots: Coles Supermarkets; Madame Tussaud's; Warwick Castle; Orkin; Lux; Marine Corps; Kellogg's Special K; Siemens; NTL; Royal Air Force; Ford; J&B
    - Thompson Total Manning (Burt Manning tribute), undated (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL00704-VHS-015)
    - Thompson Total Manning (Burt Manning tribute), undated (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL00704-VHS-016)
    - Benchmark 2000, undated (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL00704-Bcam-001)
    - Competitive Comparative Advertising, 1999 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL00704-Bcam-002)
    - Ford Motor Company History Reel--Car, undated (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL00704-Bcam-003)
    - JWTwo--Benchmark 2000, undated (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL00704-Bcam-004)
    - Television Commercials, 2000 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL00704-Bcam-005)
      18 spots: Ford; Kraft; Unilever; Nestle; Shell; Kellogg's; Merrill Lynch; Philip Morris; Qwest; UDV; Siemens; Red Rose; Marine Corps; Heineken; Nike; De Beers; KPMG
    - Working Mom Age 25, San Francisco (Burt Manning project), undated (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL00704-Hi8-001)
    - Working Mom Age 39, San Francisco (Burt Manning project), undated (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL00704-Hi8-002)
  - Audiocassettes, 1994-1996; 10
    - Chris Jones--Duke Leadership Training, 1996 (Box AV5, Audio-cassette RL00704-CS-001)
    - Chris Jones--Duke Leadership Training, 1996 (Box AV5, Audio-cassette RL00704-CS-002)
    - Prepared foods interview, 1994 (Box AV5, Audio-cassette RL00704-CS-003)
    - Rolex 1995-1996 Co-Op Advertising New Radio Commercials (Box AV5, Audio-cassette RL00704-CS-004)
  - Computer discs (Hard copy available in files), 1993-2001 and undated; 11
    - Disk 001: 10 Insoluble Agency Management Issues; Word Mac 5.0; 3.5 floppy, undated (Box AV6)
    - Disk 002: Abruption for Nestle; 3.5 floppy, 1993 (Box AV6)
    - Disk 003: Atlanta Excel spreadsheets; 3.5 floppy, undated (Box AV6)
    - Disk 004: Brand. New. Ideas; 3.5 floppy, undated (Box AV6)
    - Disk 005: Burt Manning after dinner speech--European Managers Meeting; 3.5 floppy, 1996 (Box AV6)
    - Disk 006: Burt Manning--Creating Maximum Bandwidth--World Federation of Advertisers; 3.5 floppy, 1995 (Box AV6)
    - Disk 007: Competitive Comparative Advertising; 3.5 floppy, 1999 (Box AV6)
    - Disk 008: Chris Jones--Creating Impact in Advertising; Mackintosh; 3.5 floppy, 1999 (Box AV6)
    - Disk 009: Chris Jones--European School of Management; 3.5 floppy, undated (Box AV6)
    - Disk 010: Chris Jones--Europe.SPC Shell speech; Word; 3.5 floppy, undated (Box AV6)
    - Disk 011: EXCO agenda memos; 3.5 floppy, 1999 (Box AV6)
    - Disk 012: Financial Review memo; 3.5 floppy, 1999 (Box AV6)
    - Disk 013: Gus Lizuka, JWT Tokyo--You Are Part of the Plan; 3.5 floppy, undated (Box AV6)
    - Disk 014: Howard Brundage memo; 3.5 floppy, undated (Box AV6)
    - Disk 015: Jack Peters biography; 3.5 floppy, circa 1995 (Box AV6)
    - Disk 016: Management Succession text; 3.5 floppy, undated (Box AV6)
    - Disk 017: Mike Graham Digital Recommendations; 3.5 floppy, 1998 (Box AV6)
    - Disk 018: NEWCO Chicago; 3.5 floppy, 1997 (Box AV6)
    - Disk 019: Niagara Brand Summit; 3.5 floppy, undated (Box AV6)
    - Disk 020: North American Managers Meeting Action Summary; 3.5 floppy, 1998 (Box AV6)
    - Disk 021: Office of the Chief Executive (OCE) presentation; 3.5 floppy, 2001 (Box AV6)
    - Disk 022: Operations Meeting client file; 3.5 floppy, 1998 (Box AV6)
    - Disk 023: Putting Your Brand on Sponsorships; 3.5 floppy, undated (Box AV6)
    - Disk 024: Siemens Client Executive Meeting; 3.5 floppy, 1998 (Box AV6)
    - Disk 025: Strategic Development: 10 Pillars; 3.5 floppy, undated (Box AV6)
    - Disk 026: Talking Commodore; 3.5 floppy, 1994 (Box AV6)
    - Disk 027: Untitled; 3.5 floppy, undated (Box AV6)
    - Disk 028: Worldwide Executive Group; 3.5 floppy, 1997 (Box AV6)
    - Disk 029: Worldwide Executive Group--Roy Glah; 3.5 floppy, 1997 (Box AV6)
    - Disk 030: Worldwide Executive Group--Andy Fenning Knowledge and Communication; 3.5 floppy, 1997 (Box AV6)
    - Disk 031: Worldwide Executive Group--Action Summary; 3.5 floppy, 1997 (Box AV6)
    - Disk 032: WPP request--Chris Jones; 3.5 floppy, 1999 (Box AV6)
    - Disk 033: WPP Board Meeting; 3.5 floppy, 1996 (Box AV6)
    - Disk 034: Wpp Board Meeting--Burt Manning/Chris Jones charts and slides; 3.5 floppy, 1996 (Box AV6)
    - Disk 035: WPP Strategy; 3.5 floppy, undated (Box AV6)
    - Disk 036: Abruption--Nina DiSesa; 5.25 Cartridge, undated (Box AV5)